Letters, words and spacing.
In our last lesson we looked at the importance of saying something as simple as I, let's take a leap, Spy, to point out that they're two separate words.
Another part of letters, words and spacing, because on every book, the illustrator may be somewhere different, the title may be somewhere different, and in some cases they may not even list an illustrator.
The most important part of this is to say let's start from the top. Ready To Read, Three Little Pigs, and there's a beautiful picture here.
Let's turn it over and see if we see anything on the back cover but in this particular book, Green Eggs and Ham is the title with the picture.
That's the author, by Dr. Seuss.
We're continually pointing out that words have spaces that are made up of letters.
We start from the top and work our way to the bottom.
The next concept is turning the page.
The word open the cover.
Two important concepts that we're going to look at in the next lesson.